

About Me

Domiciled in Bandung City, West Java Province, Indonesia, and has experience in the Cyber Security Field (Especially Web Apps) in 2010 -2016 and continued in 2021 - now to carry out further in-depth research regarding **Vulnerabilities** Assessment and Penetration Testing. This cannot be separated Quality Assurance, Development Website, Multimedia and Artificial Intelligence expertise.

Hardskill

- Vulnerability Assesment
- Penetration Testing
- Quality Assurance
- Web Development
- Multimedia Design
- Automatic System (AI / ML)

Softskill

Dicipline, Communication, Leadership, and Teamworking



1st winner of draw in Cyber Security Competition - 2016

Universitas Komputer Indonesia

Firdamdam Sasmita

Penetration Tester of Cyber Security (Web App, Mobile App, and Network Scope)

Education

Universitas Komputer Indonesia - S.Kom. / B.Sc.

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering 2014 - 2018 | IPK: 3.52 (Cumlaude)

Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia - M.Pd. / M.Ed.

Master of Vocational Education and Technology 2019 - 2021 | IPK: 3.90 (Cumlaude) **★**

Experience

Diarium Telkom Indonesia of PT Swamedia Informatika Vendor

2021 - 2024 (now) 🕝 Telkom 鋒 🗓

Making VA&PT for 500+ of Vulnerabilities Achievement from Diarium App (Website, Mobile, API) owned by Telkom Indonesia Company. Processes Testing of Quality Assurance has been done too for this app.

Cyber Security Technician -Digital Talent Scholarship

mid. 2022 - 2023 👌

One of program talent in Indonesia called Digital Talent Scholarship has already been done and getting a full chapter of theory EC-Council (Cyber Security Technician)

Cyber Security Tutor - Yuk-Mari Project

2020 - 2024 (now)

Yuk-Mari Project Company has a program called Virtual Classroom, which is make the student or the people who wants to learn about Cyber Security, can join and watch the videos.

Supply Chain Risks - Cyber Awarness UI University

mid. 2022 - 2023 🙎 👓

Security focuses on Logistic Scope has been discovered from Cyber Awarness Program (Universitas Indonesia / UI). Theory and practice has been explained for Supply Chain Risks.

Consultant Private Speaker - CISO Indonesia

2024 Corinium

After several events has been done in 2024, the CISO Indonesia has been contacted my number and we make a private speaking for cyber security areas.

Web Penetration Tester -Cyber Army Academy

2023 CYBER ACADEMY

Cyber Academy has one program and openend a class for who wants to learn more about information security, like knowledge basic, simulation labs, or certification exam.

Contact & Language

Contact

Calling me Adam Sasmita

Phone: +62 813 8636 9207

Email: firdamdamsasmita@upi.edu

Linked In: Adam Sasmita

Language

Indonesian, Sunda, English